I sell dental services.
We do about 25 million a year in revenue.
What's stopping me mainly is talent acquisition.
If I have a specialized one-time role,
headhunters all the way.
They already have networks to that,
I don't wanna rebuild that.
If I'm doing a repeated role that is core to my business,
so let's say I'm a media company and I need editors,
I wanna have a very well-defined process
of recruiting, hiring, onboarding, training editors.
If I have my sales-driven company,
then I wanna have a really good process
of recruiting, hiring, training, onboarding salespeople.
I don't wanna outsource that
because it's core to the economic engine that I have.
Makes sense.
I think for you, dentists is core
to the economic engine.
Front desk people is probably core to the economic engine.
Those two roles are gonna be things
that would probably make sense
to have a specialized person who focuses on that.
My favorite way to do this is just go find a firm
that does it, go in the LinkedIn,
and go one level lower to a person
who's actually doing it and say,
hey, I wanna do that thing just for me
instead of 10 other people,
and I'll pay you better and treat you better.